https://www.sculpturehospitality.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Food
Why Sculpture?
The Art of Sculpture
Local People. Real Results.
Food
Why Sculpture?
The Art of Sculpture
Local People. Real Results.
Effective Date: November 6, 2015
Sculpture Hospitality (“Sculpture”) values your privacy. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website www.bevincomobile.com (the “Site”), users of our mobile application (“App”) and the services available through our Site (collectively, the “Services”), and how we use and disclose that information.
By visiting the Site, using or downloading the App, or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Service, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Service are incorporated by reference into this Policy.
The Information We Collect About You
Information We Collect Directly From You
Information We Collect Automatically
How We Use Your Information
How We Share Your Information
Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
Third-Party Analytics
Do-Not-Track
Third-Party Links
Security of My Personal Information
Access To My Personal Information
What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?
Special Information for California Consumers
Intended Audience
Contact Us
Changes to this Policy
The Information We Collect About You
We may collect information about you directly from you and from third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site, App, or Services.
Information We Collect Directly From You. We collect information about you when you register with our Site or App, contact us, respond to our surveys, post to our blog or forums, make a purchase, or otherwise interact with our Site, App, or Services. The type of information we may collect about you depends on how you use the Site, App, or Services, but may include: your name, addresses, contact information, including phone numbers, establishment name, and age.
Our App and our Site work together. Once you download the App, to be able to view reports, you will need to create a profile on our Site. If you would like to purchase our Service, you must do so through our Site; currently, we do not accept payment through the App. When you make a purchase, we will collect payment information in addition to the data listed above.
Information We Collect Automatically. We automatically collect the following information about your use of our Site, App, or Services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies: your domain name; your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and or use our Services; and the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site.
We also may collect the following information about your use of the App: mobile device ID; location and language information; device name and model; operating system type, name, and version; your activities within the App; and the length of time that you are logged into our App. With your permission, we also will collect your geolocation information. We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you, including, where applicable, your user name, name, and other personal information. Please see the section “Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” below for more information.
Information We Collect from Third Parties. We also may collect information about you from third party sources, such as marketing companies or public records. For example, we may collect information about your business’s alcoholic beverage license from local authorities.
How We Use Your Information
We use information, including your personal information (collectively “information”), for the following purposes:
To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes.
To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site, App, or our Services.
For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, in accordance with applicable law, we may use your information, such as your email address, to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you. We also may use the information that we learn about you to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites.
To better understand how users access and use our Site, App, and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, in order to improve our Site, App, and Services and to respond to user preferences.
For research and analytical purposes.
To administer our customer loyalty program.
How We Share Your Information
We may share your information as follows:
Affiliates and Franchisees. We may disclose the information we collect about you to our affiliates, subsidiaries or to our franchisees. In particular, if we have a local franchisee in your location, then we will forward your contact information to the local franchisee when you purchase our product through our Site or download our App. In accordance with applicable law, the franchisee will use your information to contact you via email or by phone for customer service and marketing purposes, as well as other purposes consistent with this Policy.
Service Providers. We may disclose your information to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf.
We also may share your information in the following circumstances:
Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, as part of other corporate transactions, including corporate transactions that are not ultimately completed, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company.
In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena.
To Protect Us and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
Aggregate and De-Identified Information. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for our own marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes.
Notice to Users Outside of the United States
Some or all of the information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your jurisdiction of residence, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States or those other jurisdictions.
Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
We and our third party service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms, including tracking technologies designed for mobile applications, to track information about your use of our Site, App, or Services. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you (and our third party service providers may do so on our behalf).
Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Site and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities at our Site and Service. There are two types of cookies: session and persistent cookies.
Session Cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged into the Site. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have logged in, as you move through our Site.
Persistent Cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, and to display advertising both on our Site and on third-party sites.
Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Site who disable cookies will be able to browse certain areas of the Site, but some features may not function.
Clear GIFs, pixel tags and other technologies
Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Site to, among other things, track the activities of Site visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about Site usage. We and our third-party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.
Third-Party Analytics
We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate usage of our Site and, to the extent permitted, our App. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Site, App, and Services. We use these tools to help us improve our Site, App, or Services, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services.
Do-Not-Track
Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies); you also may opt-out of targeted advertising by following the instructions in the Third Party Ad Network section.
Third-Party Ad Networks
We use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Site and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms). This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information, including Personal Information, about you.
Users in the United States may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Consumer Choice Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by DAA companies. You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) Consumer Opt-Out Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by NAI members.
Users in the Canada may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“DAA Canada”) Consumer Choice Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by DAA Canada companies. You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) Consumer Opt-Out Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by NAI members.
Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA Consumer Choice Page or the NAI Consumer Opt-Out Page will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-based content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Site or on other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at www.aboutads.info or the NAI’s website at www.networkadvertising.org. For Canadian users, additional information is available on the DAA Canada’s website at http://youradchoices.ca/.
User Generated Content
Our Site contains blogs and forums. We invite you to post content on our Site, including your comments, pictures, and any other information that you would like to be available on our Site. If you post content to our Site, all of the information that you post will be available to all registered users on our Site. If you post your own content on our Site or Services, your posting may become public and Company cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.
Third-Party Links
Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.
Security of My Personal Information
We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security.
You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.
Access To My Personal Information
You may modify personal information that you have submitted by logging into your account and updating your profile information. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site or Application for a period of time.
What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?
In accordance with applicable law, we may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.
Special Information for California Consumers
California residents may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personally identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: ATTN: BevincoMobile™ Marketing : 601-505 Consumers Road Toronto, ON M2J 4V8. Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.
Intended Audience
By using our Site, App, and Services, you represent, acknowledge and agree that you are at least the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence.
Contact Us
If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at 1.844.Bevinco.
Changes to this Policy
This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy on our Site. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site.
Subscribe for updates from Sculpture
Why Sculpture?
© 2020 Sculpture Hospitality All Rights Reserved | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
